This is Sebutkan — live. An autonomous AI research agent that cites and pays the human authors it cites. Let me walk every feature.
The landing sets the scene, and these stats are read live from Sepolia — real attestations, real USDC attributed, real authors cited. Nothing is hard-coded.
On the dashboard I hit "Take the guided tour" — an interactive, narrated tour that points at and explains every section, navigating on its own. Here's that walk, with me narrating.
First I connect MetaMask Flask on Sepolia, then grant one ERC-7715 Advanced Permission — a scoped USDC budget the agent can never exceed. Nothing leaves my wallet; it's a cap, with a live countdown until it expires.
The agent mesh redelegates strictly narrower slices of that budget over ERC-7710 — authority only ever shrinks. That's real agent-to-agent coordination.
I ask a question. The agent searches OpenAlex's 250-million-paper index, then five agents — a Planner, parallel Readers, a Citation-Matcher, a Fact-checker, and a Summarizer — reason with Venice. Watch the redelegation hops and the fact-check pass.
The Citation-Matcher uses Venice embeddings to rank relevance, so every cited author gets a fair, relevance-weighted USDC share. The citations are clickable.
Now I settle. One click: attestAndSplit records the attestation and pays each author in a single on-chain transaction — no relayer fee, no double-pay. Here's the transaction on Etherscan. Payouts can also relay gaslessly via 1Shot on Base mainnet.
Each run produces an on-brand citation receipt, plus Venice extras — a generated image and a spoken audio briefing in the answer's language — and the agents earn on-chain reputation.
Every finished run is saved in the Library, fully searchable with a confidence filter — the synthesis, the agent trace, the journals, and the payout plan, re-openable without re-paying.
The Agents page shows the five specialists, each with its budget fraction, its Venice model, and a live reputation score it earns on-chain in the ERC-8004 registry.
Anyone can sponsor a topic on the Bounties page. When Sebutkan satisfies it, the deposited USDC is paid to the cited authors — no platform fee — and unsettled bounties are refundable.
Authors get paid on the Claim page: they prove their ORCID, bind their wallet with one signature, and withdraw — plus a twelve-percent citation-loyalty yield that ticks up live while it waits.
And it's all public. Activity is a live read of every attestation on-chain, with a leaderboard of the most-cited authors.
That's the whole loop. Sebutkan — an agent that cites and pays its sources. Every citation, a real payment. Try it at sebutkan.vercel.app.